Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Commencement
  - Commencement Tickets, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Programs, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Commencement Programs, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Commencement Programs, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Graduation Roster, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Programs, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Park Permit, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Commencement Programs, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Commencement Programs, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Park Permit, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Programs, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Park Permit, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Park Permit, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Fountain Seating and Park Meetings, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Park: Agenda Notes and Permit, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Programs, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Park Permit, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Programs, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Park Permit, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Programs, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Programs, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Programs, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Programs, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Planning, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Script, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (Drizzle), 1990 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Rain Script, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Romich Memos, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Staff, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Set up/Maps, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Requisitions, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Instructions to Marshals- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Instructions to Students Procession Marshals, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Programs, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Planning, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Script, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (Drizzle), 1991 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Rain Script, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Memos, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Set-up/Maps, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Staff, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Marshal Instructions, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Instructions to Student Procession Marshals, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Instructions for Faculty Procession Marshals, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Instructions for Marshals- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Coles Planning, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Commencement Ticket, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Directory, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Programs, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Commencement Planning, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Commencement Script- Oliva, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Commencement Script, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Coles Rain Script, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Coles Rain Script- Oliva, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Catering, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Romich Memos, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Requisitions, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Instructions for Students Procession Marshals, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Commencement Programs, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Commencement Planning, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Commencement Planning, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Commencement Script- Jops, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Commencement Script- Pres. Oliva, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Commencement Script- Abbreviated Park (rain), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Commencement Script- Snow room (rain), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Seating Marshals, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Procession Marshals, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Catering, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Set-up Memos, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Post-commencement Mailing, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Script- revised 5/12/93, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Scripts w/ Prologue, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Scripts- Synopsis, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Information and Fliers, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Forms, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Instructions for Faculty Procession Marshals, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Instructions for Students Procession Marshals, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Instruction for Marshals- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Tickets and Passes, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - NYU Today- Commencement, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Programs, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Stage Manager's Park Script, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Instructions for Faculty Procession Marshals, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Instructions for Students Procession Marshals, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Instructions for Marshals- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Tickets, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Script (annotated), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Directory, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Requisitions, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Notices, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Script Synopsis, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Script- Snow Room (rain), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Stage Manager's Abbreviated Park Script (rain), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (rain), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Commencement Instructions Mailing, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Mailing, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Order Forms, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Planning, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Script- Oliva, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Script w/ Cues, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Drizzle Script (annotated), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Memos, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Catering, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Set-up/Maps, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Staff, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Trustees Dinner, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Programs, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Commencement Planning, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Valedictory Speech- Momplaisir, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Commencement Script, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Stage Manager's Park Script, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Script- Oliva, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (drizzle), 1995 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Snow Script and Set-Up (rain), 1995 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Memos, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Catering, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Set-up/Maps, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Staff, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Trustee Dinner, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Instructions to Marshals, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Directory, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Tiffany ink pen with silver torch, 2007
    Scope and Contents
    ID Number: 433. Description: Tiffany ink pen with silver torch. Creator/Donor/Subject: Office of Commencement and Special Events (RG 7.4).
  - Commencement and Grad Alley Programs, Scripts, Tickets, Badges, Hats, and Mailings, 2016 (Box 43, Folder 5-8)
  - Commencement and Grad Alley Programs, Invitations, and Mailings, 2018 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Academic Attire Pick-Up Cards, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Bag Check Info Card and Ticket, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Baseball Cap, 2019 (Box 116)
  - Dinners and Receptions, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Grad Alley, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Greeter Handbook, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Program, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Scripts, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Silver Professorships, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Staff Badge, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Ticket Insert Cards, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Tickets, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Yankee Stadium Map, 2019 (Box 116, Folder 14)